All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm going to be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
There, they found themselves facing the New Fishman Pirates, who were looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom and instigated an all-out war.
After a long and grueling battle, Luffy finally defeated Hordy, the captain of the New Fishman Pirates, thwarting their plan for revenge.
There is still much you do not know. Listen closely. Before you reach the New World, you must be aware of two key changes that have occurred there.
Now then, the first matter, as I've already begun to explain, is that the Navy under Fleet Admiral Sakazuki is stronger than before.
And secondly, the Blackbeard Pirates are making strides of their own.
Ohhhh!
You idiots just had to kick him into next week, didn't you? Why couldn't you just knock him out and tie him up in the tower?
Oh, Nami, you're so cute!
Go catch him and bring him back!
We're here to collect for Big Mom. We can't face them now.
We don't have any sweets for this month's payment. Hordy and his lackeys tore the factory apart.
And all the candy we could salvage was sent to the banquet so the Straw Hats could enjoy it. What should we do?
Something tells me Big Mom of the Four Emperors won't be satisfied with an apology. That woman would level an entire country for sweets.
She loves sweets. Big Mom of the Four Emperors.
After much celebration, the banquet finally comes to an end.
They're seriously gonna let us keep all that treasure?!
Cool!
That's pretty generous!
Do you think Luffy and the others are alright, Nami? I'm so worried.
Eh, they're fine.
We're gonna be fancy rich pirates now!
Woo! It sounds nice, but something tells me this is too good to be true.
Hey, Usopp! Why don't we go look for the treasure thief too?
Uh, how about no? I found out that guy's bounty is over 200 million, so he's not gonna be an easy target!
Whoa! And mine's only 50 berries!
Hey, Zoro! Sanji! Check it out! Easiest treasure hunt ever!
That one punch knocked him out cold. I almost feel bad for him.
And he left all this loot sitting out in the open.
Neptune's gonna let us keep all this? I guess he really is as goofy as he looks.
Awesome! How much meat do you think this'll buy?
To think his body could hold all this. I mean, I know he's made a sludge, but still.
One, two, three!
Let's take it back to the palace!
Ow!
We need a flying fish!
Which way to town, Zoro?
That way.
Or we could always run off with the loot.
What?!
Well, Minister of the Left?
Please have mercy, Mr. Pecos.
Hordy and his crew attacked the factory, and now we don't have any candy left.
And what makes any of that our problem?
You're supposed to pay us in candy each month in exchange for using Mama's name.
Don't tell me you've forgotten about our little agreement.
And I was planning on taking some sweets for myself.
Which means now I'm mad and hungry.
We've done business with you for a long time, so I hate to say this, but...
I don't think I need to remind you how scary Mama can be when she's angry.
She'll kill you!
Look at those cute little eyes!
You'd better pay up! Right now!
Huh? What's going on?
Huh?
Hey!
This is the candy factory Papa Goo told me about!
Yeah?
Hopefully we can find a flying fish around here.
This must be the place where they make that candy I like so much!
Hey guys!
Are you gonna give us a grand tour?
Ho ho! Straw Hat Luffy!
Oh my god, hi!
Like, is the banquet over?
Luffy?
Why isn't she here?
Uh huh?
Dude, I totally pigged out too!
Fishman Island's got all kinds of delicious food, but that candy was unbelievable!
Ooh!
One, two, three!
Gah!
What's that?!
Whoa, whoa!
Wixnay on the Andy K!
Don't say anything!
Oh!
Hey, it's Mr. Catfish!
What are you up to?
He said candy!
Candy!
Just who is this guy?
Hmm...
Huh!
That Straw Hat Luffy, no doubt about it!
He's got no business here!
He's a pirate, right?
Well, sorry, you see he is...
Listen here, kid!
Tell me what candy you're talking about!
I can explain, Mr. Pickles!
Actually...
Hey, I don't know you!
You're not a fish man!
Are you here for sweets too?
I'm right there with you, buddy!
I can't get enough of them either!
You what?!
Alright, that's it!
Did that brat just say what I think he said?
Well, uh...
I assure you there's an explanation!
Awesome!
I've never seen a talking lion!
Eh, it's no big deal!
We have a fluffy animal guy too!
Gesundheit?
Are you sick?
Uh, no!
Guess someone's talking about me!
That's just silly!
Sorry, but it's kinda hard to take you seriously!
What'd you say, pal?
I'll make you regret that!
Get off!
Don't laugh at me!
You little...
Peccombs...
Threatening this monsieur will not bring us any closer to the sweets, mon frere.
The tea party is in four days.
Let us try to avoid a faux pas.
If we have to wait here until morning, well...
C'est la vie!
You're just as weird as he is!
What's your name?
Mmm...
Bonjour!
Enchanté!
Mes amis parrettes!
Je suis Baron Tamago!
I am pleased to make your acquaintance!
Tamago?
He he he he he he he!
He he he he...
Ugh!
Oui!
Take care to remember my name, s'il vous plaît.
Now, excusez-moi, messieurs.
Am I to comprend that you have devoured all the sweets in the factory, my little bon vivant?
Did you get that?
Yep, that was me. I could go for some more right about now.
Unfortunately, the candies have met their denouement.
Huh?
Attends, that is the jolly roger of our boss, Charlotte Lin-Lin, also known as Big Mom of the Four Emperors.
That symbol indicates that this island is Mama's territory, d'accord?
You see, Mama owns the place, which means Fishman Island is under Big Mom's protection.
That's a nice thing to do. I like your boss already. Kind of weird name, though.
Au contraire, mon ami. This is a business deal.
Huh?
We allow them the protection of our mark, and in exchange, they have to pay Mama ten tons of sweets every month.
That's a lot.
Oui, monsieur. There is nothing in this world Mama loves more than sweets.
Mama says sweets from Fishman Island are like creme de la creme, you know.
Pay up tomorrow, and we will bid you adieu.
I'm sorry, sir, but I told you before, the machinery used to make the candy was badly damaged.
It'll take us at least two weeks to make the repairs. We won't be ready tomorrow.
That is not our problem, monsieur.
Hey, fancy! Why can't you just wait a while?
Yeah, why doesn't your boss have the balls to come talk to us himself? He's one of the Four Emperors, isn't he?
Where are your manners? Our leader happens to be a madame pirate and a fearsome one at that.
That said, I do not think Mama has the balls.
It's a girl? That's different, then.
I love sweets. I just can't resist the things. And I really love men who can make them.
Anyway, what if your boss lady doesn't get her candy?
In that case...
Voila! The deal is off. The big mum parrots will attack en masse, and you can say so long and bonsoir to this island, miserable.
You want to destroy the island? How crazy can you be? You can't do that over some stupid candies.
Please? I won't let you. We just saved this place, you know.
You seem so happy, Mama.
Yes, it's only four days until the tea party. I can hardly wait.
I'll finally be able to taste those delightful candies from Fishman Island.
I'm so excited my stomach is already producing all the acid I'll need.
Candy, candy, Fishman Island candy.
I see you are all excited, too.
Of course, Mama. That's the best candy there is.
Then wait for them in my stomach, because that's where they're all going to go.
Roar!
Mama!
I'm home now!
Roar!
Oh, Bobbin, how did your mission go?
I set the whole place on fire!
That's wonderful to hear.
That country's baked goods were the best in the world.
I bet it smelled so delicious as it burned.
It's a shame we had to do it.
But they should have honored our agreement.
Can I have a snack?
If they can't pay in sweets, they pay with their lives.
There's one thing I can't stand.
It's a broken promise.
That and bitter candy, of course.
Oh, that reminds me.
Apparently Fishman Island can't send the payment right now.
Peckholms just told me all about it.
Should I burn that down too?
I want my Fishman Island sweets.
Get those fools on the Transponder Snail now!
You want to destroy Fishman Island?
Are you guys out of your minds?
You can't do that over some stupid candies!
I won't let you!
We just saved this place, you know!
I won't let you know!
I'm so sorry!
What could I do?
I was going to get to eat this bike in a company.
Iasp it out in the商品, which is better than us.
I'll take that drink.
I cannot believe my ears.
Their brains must be scrambled like eggs in an omelette.
This is quite a unique coup de théâtre.
Whatever are we to do with them?
I already told mama.
She's probably calling in to check on us.
Really?
No, not Big Mom.
She's scary.
You talk to her, Egghead.
She isn't going to like this at all.
Yeah, what's up?
Who is this?
It's Big Mom, right?
What are you doing?
Stop!
You don't sound like Tamago.
Or Pecums.
Who is this?
My name is Monkey D. Luffy.
Soon to be king of the pirates.
Was all that really necessary?
Oh, no moving.
Nice going.
Monkey D.
Ah.
So you must be Garp's grandson.
I remember you, young man.
You're the little upstart who interfered with the war two years ago.
There's no more candy.
Huh?
They can't send you any.
So I heard correctly.
They're supposed to have 10 tons.
Will I eat it all?
It's gone now.
Ah!
You didn't have to tell her that.
What did he just say?
Error!
Oh, sorry!
Oh, no more candy!
Hey!
Oh, my God!
Jeremy!
Ah!
Oh, my God!
Oh!
We're here!
Ho!
Oh!
Oh, my God!
Don't you lie to me, you stupid child!
You'd better not be covering for those weak fishmen!
I'm not lying! It was all me!
I didn't know they were supposed to be for you!
I'll make you a deal! We've got a bunch of treasure!
If I give it to you, then can we call it even?
Seriously?!
What?! I can't eat gold and diamonds, can I?
Sweets are the only treasures that mean anything to me!
A minute, monsieur! Are those really full of treasure?
Yeah, they are!
Pardonnez-moi, maman! Let's think about it, no?
So, alors? Only a few short days ago,
that enfant terrible, Captain Kidd,
took down deux of our allies' vessels, n'est-ce pas?
Kid what now?
You know, that rookie we met at Sub Aode, who's worth a hundred million.
It was a disaster!
We suffered a major financial setback,
and we could certainly stun ze monetary assistance!
And no candies are your raison d'être,
but if you ask moi, the best option is to accept ze treasure in lieu of sweets payments for now.
You'll only have to wait a couple of weeks to collect your confections, D'accord?
If you really want something sweet, we can always pick up some bonbons for you on the way back.
Huh?
Do you invite yourself, top uncle?
I don't think you even suggest something like that!
What kind of poor excuse for a pirate compromises on what she wants most?
Oi! Please forgive me, Mama!
Be that as it may...
This insolent pirate who ate all my sweets intrigues me!
Forget Fishmen Island!
Now that you've chosen to go against me,
I'll just have to get my revenge on you instead!
Luffy and the others should be back by now!
I have a bad feeling, Mommy.
What if they're hurt?
You're right.
It is taking them a long time.
What did those goofballs get themselves into now?
If they come back without that treasure,
it will not be pretty!
Well then, Monkey D. Luffy...
Now that I know who you are...
Come here!
Let's chat in the new world!
She means to kill him!
Sure thing! Be there soon!
I've got something I need to settle with you too!
Hmm?
I like this island!
It's too risky to trust you with it!
Once I get there...
I'm gonna kick your ass!
And then I'll make Fishmen Island my territory!
Little brat!
The crisis on Fishmen Island is averted for now,
but a secret hidden inside their royal treasure,
the Tomate Box,
may cause trouble with Big Mom when Luffy reaches the New World.
However, she is but one of many foes
that the Straw Hats have to worry about.
An old adversary has made a move to new waters,
and it's only a matter of time
until they're forced to face off again.
On the next,
One Piece!
Many problems lie ahead!
A trap awaiting in the New World!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!